Create a 500mm x 800mm plate
Use the positioning ball to position it near the
backrest
Select the outer line of the plate and use the inner line support function to create the inner line for folding
Then choose the fold arrangement tool to fold the two sides of the board
Then continue to open the simulation and let the blanket hang on the back
Then open the simulation and let the blanket hang on the back
Before, if the blanket is frozen,
the sheet and the model are penetrated
You can activate the simulation again
Then delete the inner line used for folding
Reduce the particle strength of the sheet and simulate
a better ک
Replace the fabric with Knit
Turn on Knit, Congratulations!
Ponte Jersey